Hello Hello, we’ve
Здравствуйте
already talked to you a couple of
Здравствуйте общались уже с вами пару
times, yes. It was, in my opinion, once
раз да Было по-моему один раз
constructively, one joked, I
конструктивно один стебался я до
maybe, maybe, or two times,
может быть может или два раза стебался
maybe even joked 3
может быть даже 3
Look so seriously If we talk
Вот смотри так серьезно Если поговорить
You saw yesterday’s attacks on
Вот вы видели вчерашние удары по
Sevastopol on the headquarters of the Black Sea Fleet
севастополю по штабу Черноморского флота
Yes, today’s  topic I didn’t watch
Да сегодняшняя тема я не смотрел сами
these blows themselves
эти удары
[music] I
[музыка]
read the article and what’s the article
статью читал а что там статьи
Well about the fact that this is your last hope to
Ну о том что это ваша последняя надежда
somehow support your society
как-то поддержать ваше общество
so today is new
поэтому сегодня новое
[music] of
[музыка]
the week
недели
submarine And now
подводную лодку А теперь
in general it doesn’t come anywhere now only
Вообще нигде не наступает теперь только
with every  every week Ukraine more and
с каждым с каждой неделю Украина все
more
больше больше
For example,
Например
if your president said that he would
если ваш президент сказал что он будет
swim in the Crimea
купаться в Крыму
[music]
[музыка]
And so it turned out that it is constantly changing and
А так получилось постоянно меняется и
this is
это
Why it is changing, look at our president,
Почему меняется смотрите наш президент в
including like our bud, this is a
том числе как и наш бутоном это
professional type, they all
профессиональный типшники они все так
say that, not for me, they  they say something
говорят не для меня они что-то говорят
for the people in Crimea,
для людей в Крыму
the Russians, all sorts of collaborators for the
российские всяких коллаборантов для
people in the Kremlin are not for the people. The thing is,
людей в Кремле не для людей Дело в том
look very simply, it’s clear that they wo
что смотрите очень просто ясно что День
n’t call you the Day of the Liberation of Crimea, just
освобождения Крыма вам не назовут также
as they didn’t call the Day of the Liberation of
как не называли День освобождения
Kherson, they just took it and came in later
Херсона просто взяли и зашли потом
and what not, they came in before  now Kherson And what does
а что нет зашли до сих пор Херсоне А что
n’t result is not so important
не в результате не так не важно
at all, why bother with the
вообще
most difficult battles if you can
зачем зачем сложнейшие бои если можно по
knock out warehouses and knock out a drink using the art of war
военному искусству выбить склады выбить
?
Ладно ладно если Главное чтобы ваш
really
крут И все пруд это главное реально
cool everyone needs him not as a showman he’s very
круты всем нужен не он как шоумен очень
handsome yes he’s playing out his role
красавчик да он отыгрывает роль свою
Well done they’re giving us more and more I
Молодец нам дают все больше и больше
see six months ago they said that
Смотрю еще полгода назад сказать что
British Storm Shadow missiles would
британские ракеты Шторм Shadow будут вот
freely roam around the Crimea in short
так свободно ебашить по Крыму короче
it was brazen in short In broad daylight in
нагло это вообще было Средь бела дня
short Holy [ __ ] there  this is a video of how
короче [__] там это видео как
one arrives people are filming the
прилетает одна люди снимают прилетают
second one arrives it’s just a thrill I’m glad that
вторая это просто это кайф Я рад что у
you’re in a good mood
вас хорошее настроение
I was so inspired yesterday
Я вчера вообще был настолько
I went out into the street my friends walk around
я вышел на улицу знакомые ходят
everyone greets each other as you know The
все приветствуют друг друга как знаешь
Crimean bridge was a cruiser
Крымский мост был крейсером
very good If we’re watching Why we
очень хорошо Если мы смотрим Что
closed our eyes  there is some kind of
зажмурились там вашего какого-то этого
head of the Black Sea Fleet being squeezed or
начальника Черноморского флота жмут или
an officer
офицера
if We open it, I can for example,
если Мы открываем вот я могу например
there are 12 confirmed Russian
есть 12 подтвержденных российских
generals who have already been identified as
генералов которые идентифицированы уже
Ukrainian, not a single one can you name the
украинского ни одного не можете назвать
deceased general,
погибшего генерала
that is, in fact, in fact,
то есть на самом деле вот на самом деле
I will say this, I admire the fortitude  of your
я скажу так я восхищен стойкостью вашего
people, your country is actually smeared,
народа ваша страна фактически размазана
but you believe and it’s admirable, that is,
но вы верите и это восхищает то есть
how much. Our peoples, I
насколько насколько Вот наши народы я
still don’t divide us too much, although you
все-таки нас не сильно разделяю хоть вы
may have a different opinion about
может быть и по-другому считаете
how resilient our people are and
насколько наши народы устойчивые и
are able to resist
способные сопротивляться
any challenge.
любым вызовом
I, for example, have never Russia  I’ve
сопротивляться Я например никогда Россия
never seen Russians
никогда не видел чтобы россияне
holding a rally. For example,
митинговали Например
I saw. If you say
я видел Если говорить
[ __ ] the Tsarist regime into communism and then
нахер Царский режим в коммунизм а потом
turn it back to capitalism, there is no other regime like that
отвернуть в капитализм нет другой такой
at all,
вообще
not Russian, they drank When different
режим не русский бухали Когда разные
nations poured out the Tsarist regime, they
народы вылили Царский режим
were absolutely revolutionized, the Ukrainians were like
были революционировалось украинцы типа
who, Lenin, Russian canes, Stalin, Russian
кто Ленин трости русский Сталин русский
Well, which of the revolutionaries  was Russian
Ну кто из революционеров был русский
Name it really, do
Назовите реально
you think it’s just like that, you know
вы считаете что это просто такая знаете
I’m just someone who is constantly
я просто который постоянно кто-то
in control I just want to ask about the
управляет Я просто хочу спросить вот из
revolutionaries who came to power in 917
революционеров которые в 917 году пришли
like the Great October Revolution Who was
власти так Великая Октябрьской Кто
Russian to listen to if the people didn’t
русский был послушать если бы народ не
want a revolution
хотели революции
Who from the top that came  there was a Russian in power
Кто из верхушки которая пришла к власти
I don’t know for sure there were some
Я не знаю наверняка какие-то были
Russians Lenin was Russian
русские Ленин был русский
I don’t know what grades he had there was a
я не знаю какие у него там были троетки
Russian
был русский
was Ulyanov
был Ульянов
Dzhugashvili was Answer me who was in the
Джугашвили был Ответьте мне кто был
Ulyanovsk region
Ульяновской области
[music]
[музыка]
So, look Maria Ulyanova of
Так ну смотрите Мария Ульянова
Swedish-German origin That  there is
шведско-немецкого происхождения То есть
he is no longer German everything That’s it Yes
он уже не немецкая все Вот именно Да
Swedish of German origin everything yes
шведская немецкого происхождения все да
And according to his father according to different versions there is That’s
А по отцу по разным версиям имеется Вот
all yes that is further I say Trotsky
и все да то есть дальше я говорю Троцкий
is not Russian
не русский
Who is Dzerzhinsky
Кто там Дзержинский вот
this is all a revolutionary Dzerzhinsky If you
это все революционер Дзержинский Если вы
Now take the list
Сейчас возьмем список
None of the prominent Here  who really
Никто из видных Вот кто реально
shot it
это застрелило
Rosa Luxemburg was Russian that Russian
Роза Люксембург была русская что русский
Why must they be visible, but it’s
Почему обязательно должны быть видны вот
not visible, tell me the Russians are not visible
не видно скажите мне не видно
Revolutions, the
русские Революции
first people’s Commissars of Internal
первый народный Комиссаров внутренних
Affairs of the RSFSR But this is Lenin’s predecessor
дел РСФСР Но это предшественник Ленина
as chairman of the Soviet
на должности председателя советских
People’s Commissars
народных комиссаров
before that
до этого
in Why hear Viktor Chernov It was
в А зачем слышать Виктор Чернов Это был
Chairman of the Council of People's Commissars
председатель совета народных комиссаров
who are these people For the first time I hear Lev Kamenev
кто эти люди Впервые слышу Лев Каменев
the stone is definitely not Russian the stone is not
камень точно не русский был камень не
Russian
русский
surname in any case
фамилия во всяком случае
Here is his successor
Вот его преемник уже
Dmitry Ivanovich Kursky
Курский Дмитрий Иванович
Lev Borisovich stone so the family
Лев Борисович камень так семейная
surname is Rosenfeld you have any more
фамилия розенфельд у вас есть еще
questions stone Well no of course
вопросы камень Ну нет конечно
Dmitry Kursky here's another  there is one
Дмитрий Курский вот еще есть один
functionary
функционеров
that a
что еще
non-Russian
не русский
Russian could have turned the Tsar there, and in
русский могли там и царя свернуть и того
short, the buzz is just a thrill,
короче кайф просто кайф
put it plus 100 got high from this
поставьте плюс 100 кайфанул с этой
roast
прожарочки
I don’t know, I’m high on the
Я не знаю я я кайфую
Russians, they couldn’t even turn the Tsar for
русский даже царя не могли свернуть за
them, not the Russians, they all made us drink 6
них не русские все делали пить по 6 нами
kilograms straight  at a time it’s autumn and the butts of the
килограмм прям за раз осень а попок
souls and even more I will desire YouTube, driving us
душ и дуже возжелу YouTube загоняя нас
through the quarries into a shadow ban and even more was
через карьерки в теневый бан и дуже была
that video is not shown to people,
то видео не показывается людям часто
information about streams is often shown in
показывается информация про стримы для
order for a low-speed whistle to
того чтобы мало оперативный свисток
be preferred right at once and the butt is there in a
предпочтится прям за раз а попок там в
kilogram okrim video
килограмме окрим видео
information and we  with you
информация и мы с вами
[music]
[музыка]